chartsbin.com 2016-04-01

# About ChartsBin.com

ChartsBin™ is an online information service provided by WEB APPLICATION SERVICE PROVIDER (WEBASP).

## Website Privacy Policy

This web site is owned and operated by the Web Application Service Provider (WEBASP) and will be referred to as "We", "our" and "us" in this Privacy Policy. By using this site, you agree to the Privacy Policy of this web site ("www.chartsbin.com"), which is set out on this web site page. The Privacy Policy relates to the collection and use of personal and other information you may supply to us through your conduct on this web site.

We respect the privacy of our customer and the privacy of their data. We believe that by respecting your privacy we will earn the opportunity to build a lasting relationship with you.

## Data Collection

We collect the name of those who post messages to our comment section, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail and/or contact us page, anonymous usage information on what pages user access or visit, information volunteered by the user, such as survey information and/or site registrations, comments you make in our comment section and store Data, Charts/Maps you provide or create.

## Data Use and Disclosure

The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded, used to improve the content of our web page.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

All information you provide to us will only be used for the purpose for which it was submitted. Under no circumstances will your information be shared with, or sold to, or disclosed to any third party, except where required by law or unless explicitly requested by you.

## Web-Server Logs and Cookies

On using this web site your browser automatically discloses, and our web-server automatically logs. This information includes: Internet Protocol address, browser type, referring pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click stream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies are required to use this web site. We use cookies to assist in delivering the Service and to provide a positive and personalized user experience. Our persistent and session ID cookies are used to identify unique visitors to our sites and to provide you with easy access to your files. If you have your browser set to reject cookies, your usage of the Service and this web site is likely to be interrupted.

## Advertising on ChartsBin

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of: [google](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

## Changes to this Policy

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to modify or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. This Privacy Policy is in addition to any other terms and conditions applicable to the web site.

We may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by posting a prominent notice on this web site. We do not intend to reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Each version of this Policy will be identified at the bottom of the page by its effective date.

## Questions

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or WEBASP's treatment of your personal information, should be addressed to info [at] chartsbin.com

## updated: 27 June 2011
